[{"answer": "That's a very good question.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "Tell us -- the latest mood, I guess, that people want to sense is what is President Assad's reaction likely to be to any strike that comes?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Yes, that debate has actually changed over the past couple of days, as well, and some of the video that we're seeing right now is one of the reasons.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "And there is incontrovertible evidence to that effect?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Well, my political judgment is that the administration will not do a lot.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "General Kimmitt, from a military perspective, what do you believe is the most likely military action that President Obama will take and how effective, in your experience, do you think it will be?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "Well, I think it will be effective if the object is to deter Assad from using chemical weapons again and to deter others around the world from feeling that this is now the new norm, that chemical weapons are just another tool in the military toolbox.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Adam Schiff, I mean, if that is correct, and that seems to be the perceived wisdom about what may be coming, if it's not going to be that effective and isn't really going to dismantle the Assad regime, which is something that most people have been calling for for quite some time now, what's the point of it other than making some kind of political statement?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Well, I think the main reason that President Obama has not been more decisive is indeed that the public -- the public has no appetite for some kind of broader international military engagement in Syria.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "How dangerous is that for President Obama and indeed other world leaders?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "That's right, Piers.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "And if he is, why are we not trying to seek to change his regime?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Yes, you can, Nick.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "Can I pipe in?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "In my heart of hearts, I think that Hannah perhaps got herself into a situation that she couldn't get herself out of, and I do believe that my brother gave his life to protect her.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "What do you think happened?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Do you really believe that, Laura?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Well, let's start with the first thing that you went over, the booby trapping of the house.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Why would he do all this if he was a completely innocent man?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "That he was in a shootout with police?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Well, I know one thing for sure.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "You don't believe that, either?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "In Idaho?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Fair enough.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "I mean, that's not what a man of his age should be doing?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "I know that he thought of Hannah as a daughter.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Have you answered that to yourself?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "You were -- you were very close to James?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "He was my best friend.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "How close?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "Well, again, we're coming back to -- I'm still seeing no evidence, no -- the sheriffs -- the San Diego sheriffs have basically said that the case is closed.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "I've got to put that to you that you just don't want to believe that your brother could be capable of such a monstrous act as the police believe he committed?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "If it wasn't him, who was it?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "I'm not going to speak to that.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "You think she's just lying?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "I remember very vividly telling my brother, she's trouble.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "What do you mean?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Yes.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Piers, can I stop you?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "No, I -- I think that, you know, in many ways, they're very different situations.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Do you think that was linked in some way?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "You know, the only thing that I could say to that is that Jim was very quiet.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "But was there anything in his behavioral pattern over the years where you thought potentially one day, he could crack up?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Certainly is a possibility -- anything is a possibility...", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "I mean, is it a possibility?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "Well, they have a right to their own opinion.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "What is your reaction?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "To this day, I have not asked the Andersons.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "And if so, why did you do that?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "We'll see when the time comes.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "And do you intend to?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "No, it was not.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Was that a surprise to you?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "So that was...", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "Did Brett -- did Brett believe that James had done all this?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "I think he was a little -- he was a little surprised.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "Did he tell you that?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Great.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Morgan, how are you?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "So you're -- you're now the world's pop expert because you made this movie that the entire world's teenage force is clamoring to watch.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "How are you, man?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "I think that the fact that you and I are actually having a conversation about it has proven that she accomplished everything she's set out to do.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "And so what is -- what is your reaction to the great twerking controversy involving Miley Cyrus?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Well, I think -- I think the biggest thing you've hit on is that it is a machine.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "It's so important, isn't it, to the brands of these young pop stars?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "It's been pretty wild (ph).", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "Piers?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "PURLOCK: To have the chance to make like a blockbuster, a -- a documentary blockbuster, a film that would appeal to such a major -- major audience was something I was really excited about.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "Why did you do this?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "I mean, and the biggest thing for me is you want to make sure that all the information you're getting is accurate.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "What do you make of what is happening here?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "And -- and it goes immediately.", "docId": "130827pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "The trust goes, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 618}]